<archimate:Node
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="[SBB] CIFS file server"
    id="EAID_BA99EF5C_DB4D_4682_A32D_02D28DD82E0E"
    documentation="Het betreft:&#xA;home directories van gebruikers&#xA;afdelingsdata&#xA;applicatiedata (taakmanager?)&#xA;&#xA;Momenteel zijn er ongeveer 40 Windows Fileservers in Groningen. &#xA;In zoetermeer staan ongeveer 20 File servers voor de KA-omgeving. In november 2016 wordt besloten wat hiermee zal gaan gebeuren.&#xA;&#xA;Features that CIFS offers are:&#xA;Integrity and Concurrency    CIFS allows multiple clients to access and update the same file while preventing conflicts by providing file sharing and file locking. File sharing and file locking is the process of allowing one user to access a file at a time and blocking access to all other users. These sharing and locking mechanisms can be used over the Internet and intranets. They also permit aggressive caching and read-ahead and write-behind without loss of integrity. File caches of buffers must be cleared before the file is usable by other clients. These capabilities ensure that only one copy of a file can be active at a time, preventing data corruption.&#xA;Optimization for Slow Links    The CIFS protocol has been tuned to run well over slow-speed dial-up lines. The effect is improved performance for users who access the Internet using a modem.&#xA;Security    CIFS servers support both anonymous transfers and secure, authenticated access to named files. File and directory security policies are easy to administer.&#xA;Performance and Scalability    CIFS servers are highly integrated with the operating system, and are tuned for maximum system performance.&#xA;Unicode File Names    File names can be in any character set, not just character sets designed for English or Western European languages.&#xA;Global File Names    Users do not have to mount remote file systems, but can refer to them directly with globally significant names (names that can be located anywhere on the Internet), instead of ones that have only local significance (on a local computer or LAN). Distributed File Systems (DFS) allows users to construct an enterprise-wide namespace. Uniform Naming Convention (UNC) file names are supported so a drive letter does not need to be created before remote files can be accessed.&#xA;Distributed File System (DFS) allows administrators to group shared folders located on different servers by transparently connecting them to one or more DFS namespaces."/>
